<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
  <string name="app_name">Paik</string>
  <string name="app_description">Paik is a secure news reader and reporter app featuring group conversations around news.</string>
  <string name="title_activity_main">Paik</string>
  <string name="title_activity_help">Paik</string>
  <string name="title_activity_downloads">Paik</string>
  <string name="title_activity_add_feed">Paik</string>
  <string name="title_activity_add_post">Paik</string>
  <string name="title_activity_panic">Paik</string>
  <string name="title_activity_comments">Comments</string>
  <string name="title_activity_view_media">Paik</string>
  <string name="title_activity_settings">Paik</string>
  <string name="title_activity_lock_screen">Paik</string>
  <string name="title_activity_create_account">Paik</string>
  <string name="story_list_hint_no_shared_text1">The stories shared with you using Paik Nearby are listed here.</string>
  <string name="help_title">About Paik</string>
  <string name="help_tor_title">Go Online with Tor</string>
  <string name="help_tor_content">Tor is an open network that helps keep you safe online. It defends against network surveillance that threatens your personal freedom and privacy. You will use the Orbot app to connect to the Tor network.</string>
  <string name="help_wipe_content">Tap the panic button to delete your personal data within Paik. You can set the panic action to delete the entire app in your settings.</string>
  <string name="help_share_content">Share stories, feeds and the entire app using Paik Nearby. It\'s safe, easy and only requires a friend nearby with Bluetooth. App sharing requires a WiFi network or hotspot.</string>
  <string name="help_chat_title">Talk About the News</string>
  <string name="help_chat_content">Chat with the Paik community using Paik Talk.</string>
  <string name="help_data_content">Tips to reduce your data consumption:\n\n1. Sync only the feeds that matter to you most. Paik allows you to sync individual feeds.\n\n2. Choose Bit Wise syncing mode in your settings. This syncs only text, with the ability to load photos on a story by story basis.\n\n3. Expire your articles in a timely manner. Choose your time frame in your settings.</string>
  <string name="help_terms_group_title">Terms and Software Licenses</string>
  <string name="help_terms_title">Terms and Software Licenses</string>
  <string name="help_terms_content">User-Submitted Materials\n\nBBG Websites may allow users to post, upload, transmit, or otherwise submit comments, messages, photos, images, story ideas, or other content or materials (collectively “User-Submitted Materials). You acknowledge that User-Submitted Materials may be routed through our servers, the servers of one or more third parties on our behalf, and the Internet. You acknowledge that BBG Websites are for public and not private communications.\n\nYou may only submit materials to BBG Websites for which you have the copyright or other necessary rights and permission to distribute electronically. You may not violate, plagiarize, or infringe on the rights of third parties, including copyright, patent, trademark, trade secret, privacy, personal, publicity, moral or proprietary rights. You agree and represent that you own or have all necessary rights and permissions to use, distribute, and authorize BBG to use and distribute any materials you submit.\n\nYou retain any copyright or other ownership rights you possess in any User-Submitted Materials that you submit on or through BBG Websites. However, by submitting any User-Submitted Materials on or through BBG Websites, you hereby grant BBG a non-exclusive, perpetual, royalty-free, fully paid up, worldwide, transferable license to use, copy, sublicense, modify, transmit, publicly perform, display, create derivative works of, host, index, cache, tag, encode, and/or adapt your User-Submitted Materials in any and all media formats or channels, whether now known or hereafter devised.\n\nAdditional user-submitted material Rules Specific to Posting Comments\n\nBBG will make every effort to review and post comments within 48 hours, although BBG is under no obligation to post comments within any deadline or to post the comments at all. BBG encourages thoughtful discussion and will not censor comments based on ideology or political points of view. BBG will not edit comments - we will either post them or refuse to post them. All comments must follow these rules:\n\n- Stay on topic.\n- No obscenity, profanity, vulgarity, hate language, SHOUTING, or other bad behavior.\n- No personal attacks. No inflammatory language or calls for violence.\n- No advocating or providing instruction on how to conduct any illegal activity\n- No advertising, promotional materials, "junk mail," "spam," "chain letters," "pyramid schemes," or any other form of solicitation\n- Simple text only, no html or other code.</string>
  <string name="story_comment_add_hint">Write something&#8230;</string>
  <string name="menu_chat">Paik Talk</string>
  <string name="menu_help">About</string>
  <string name="menu_search">Search</string>
  <string name="add_feed_tab_following">Following</string>
  <string name="add_feed_tab_explore">Explore</string>
  <string name="add_feed_search_hint">Search</string>
  <string name="add_feed_search_no_results">No feeds found</string>
  <string name="lock_screen_title1">Welcome to Paik</string>
  <string name="lock_screen_passphrases_not_matching">Passwords do not match, please try again</string>
  <string name="lock_screen_onboarding_1_title">Your favorite RSS feeds in one spot</string>
  <string name="lock_screen_onboarding_1_info">Discover important and entertaining stories from any source. Read in privacy. Enjoy offline access.\n\nMake it yours!</string>
  <string name="lock_screen_onboarding_1_next">Next</string>
  <string name="lock_screen_onboarding_1_language">Language</string>
  <string name="lock_screen_proxy_title">Privacy matters</string>
  <string name="lock_screen_proxy_psiphon_info">Access everything on the internet with <b>Psiphon</b>.</string>
  <string name="lock_screen_proxy_psiphon_connect">USE PSIPHON</string>
  <string name="lock_screen_proxy_psiphon_connected">Connected to Psiphon!</string>
  <string name="lock_screen_proxy_tor_info">Access everything and conceal your identity with <b>Tor</b>.</string>
  <string name="lock_screen_proxy_tor_connect">USE TOR</string>
  <string name="lock_screen_proxy_tor_connected">Connected to Tor!</string>
  <string name="lock_screen_proxy_skip">Skip</string>
  <string name="lock_screen_proxy_no_net_info">No Connection.</string>
  <string name="lock_screen_proxy_no_net_retry">Retry</string>
  <string name="lock_screen_curate_feed_title">Curate your daily feed.</string>
  <string name="change_passphrase_not_matching">Passwords do not match, please try again</string>
  <string name="post_sign_in_title">Share the news that’s happening around you</string>
  <string name="post_sign_in_info">Paik provides a feed of noteworthy news to its community. Every post created with Paik will undergo a curation process before it is shared in the official Paik news feed. Please see the Terms &amp; Conditions ("About Paik" then "Terms &amp; Software Licenses) to understand the rights you grant when you share information with Paik.</string>
  <string name="httpd_app_sender_instructions">To share the Paik app or the apps supported by it (Orbot and ChatSecure) with people nearby, please take the following steps:</string>
  <string name="bluetooth_send_info">Your friend must have the Paik app open to the \'Receive a Share\' screen from the side menu.</string>
  <string name="bluetooth_receive_title">Receive a story from a friend using Paik Nearby.</string>
  <string name="create_account_title">Create your Paik Nickname</string>
  <string name="story_list_hint_tor_title">Welcome to your Paik news feed.</string>
  <string name="story_list_hint_tor_info_psiphon">Alternatively, you can use Psiphon.</string>
  <string name="story_list_hint_tor_go_online_psiphon">CONNECT TO PSIPHON</string>
  <string name="story_list_hint_tor_more_info">Tor is not required for the news reader, however, it is strongly recommended. You can opt out of using Tor for the news, in your settings. Your privacy will not be protected in this case.\n\nTor is required for publishing reports on Paik.</string>
  <string name="story_list_hint_tor_connected_psiphon_title">You have successfully connected to Psiphon!</string>
  <string name="cacheword_notification_cached_title">Paik Unlocked</string>
  <string name="cacheword_notification_cached">Paik passcode stored in memory</string>
  <string name="cacheword_notification_cached_message">Paik passcode stored in memory</string>
  <string name="feed_category_world_news">World News</string>
  <string name="feed_category_national_news">National News</string>
  <string name="feed_category_arts_culture">Arts &amp; Culture</string>
  <string name="feed_category_business">Business</string>
  <string name="feed_category_sports">Sports</string>
  <string name="feed_category_technology">Technology</string>
  <string name="feed_category_security">Security</string>
  <string name="feed_category_discussion">Discussion</string>
  <string name="feed_category_uncategorized">Uncategorized</string>
</resources>
